Miguel Andrés Bernal Cristancho

BILINGUAL RECRUITER

+57 315602298 <u>miguel.bernal@solvoglobal.com</u>

Bogotá, Colombia

I am a Designer and Administrator, I have four years of experience in administrative assistance, Customer Service and Recruiter, I can creatively solve any problem I perceive the details and identifying problems and finding a solution, I trustworthy and work under pressure.

Education

Industrial Design

Degree

2009-2013

Universidad Jorge Tadeo Lozano Design Management

Degree 2014-2015

Universidad Jorge Tadeo Lozano

Business Administration

Degree 2017-2020

Universidad Jorge Tadeo Lozano

EXPERIENCE

Bilingual Recruiter
Jul 2022 - Currently

Solvo Global

Recruitment and selection of human talent for companies in the United States through the management of social networks.

Customer Service

Apr 2022 - Jul 2022

Atento Colombia

Facilitate customer service, Providing warmth and quality final customer. Adjusting to the requirements, protocols, procedures, and regulations defined for contacting customer services.

Quality Apprentice

Dec. 2019 - Jul 2020 Softland Colombia

Documentation, conduct customer satisfaction surveys to ensure that all documentation is up to date and is according to with company. Make calls for the personal selection process, be aware of the files and documentation of all employees, support human talent management processes and information security.

Administrative Assistant Jan. 2017 - Dec. 2019 Dinamick Studio

Perform update, registration, and Storage of information; photocopied; archived; text processing; make call and management of postal and electronic mail.

SKILLS

Languages

- English level
- * B2Native
- Spanish

Soft skills

- teamwork Skills
- * Leadership
- Communication
- * Skills Problem Solving
- Critical thinking
- Interpersonal Skills

Hard Skills

- test application
- Profile analysis
- Interview skills
- Investigation skillsManagement skills
- . Leadership Skills